<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[eLEDglance]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[eLEDglance]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/eledglance/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2016 21:00:27 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/eledglance/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[eLEDglance LED Cube (40cm) - Bluetooth remote]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>eLEDglance LED Cube (40cm) - Bluetooth remote</h1><p>This colour changing LED cube from eLEDglance is a waterproof outdoor or indoor furniture item to transform your garden or a room into a beautifully lit space! Use it to sit on or a small table to keep your drinks on. It will be the talking point of your Party!   Eye-catching and inspiring, this illuminated contemporary furniture will brighten up any relaxing space and add an atmospheric extra dimension to your entertaining! Not only can this be used as a stool, but a side table, foot rest, or simply as a futuristic light feature!  It has comfy rounded edges and a series of clever LED's discreetly fitted inside which are controlled by the remote control.   The great thing about this furniture is that the LED lights are run by a rechargeable battery, so if you don't want to power it from the mains you can go wireless!  The rechargeable battery inside the stool will give you a good eight hours of lighting without any trailing wires. When it runs out of juice, just plug it back into the mains with the supplied induction charger!</p><img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/32bd8c0e-9141-4814-9c03-29ba574828df.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/eledglance/fd39bfc6-77b3-4078-9695-27e2d2b305e4/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">fd39bfc6-77b3-4078-9695-27e2d2b305e4</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2016 20:59:58 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>Hello, Our maiden factory orders are ready and we are pleased to show you the first of our products made!</p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/eledglance/hello-our-maiden-factory-orders-are-ready-and-we-are-please/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">6929d4fc-286a-4021-be2c-27656096a0ce</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2016 09:52:55 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>